<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<document>
 <properties>
    <title>Welcome to Singularity</title>
    <author email="tom.rose@i-konect.com">Tom Rose</author>
  </properties>

  <body>
    <section name="Welcome to Singularity">
      <p>Singularity is an open source project dedicated to developing and promoting RFID
         middleware technology for use in supply chain management and the
         EPCglobal Network™. Singularity has two major components, the
         Middleware and EPC Information Service (EPC-IS).
     </p>
     <p>Singularity envisions an open source EPC-IS that is compliant with the EPCglobal™
         specification, as well as enables successful integration of EPC related
         information into the enterprise. The technology platform chosen for
         singularity is Java™ as it can be introduced into almost any corporate
         infrastructure.
     </p>
     <p>The reason for Singularity is to accelerate the evolution and adoption of RFID solutions. RFID
         Middleware and EPC-IS provides a platform that reduces entrance
         barriers, as well as provides a base to allow commercial companies to
         accelerate their product offerings. The open source approach, utilizing
         the <a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html" title="Apache 2.0 license">Apache 2.0 license</a>,
         enables end users, as well as commercial vendors, to effectively
         introduce RFID enabled supply chain management solutions into the
         enterprise.
     </p>
  
     
      <subsection name="News">
       <p style="font-size: larger; font-weight: bold">
          20 October 2005 - Singularity 1.0-M2 Release
        </p>
        <p>
         Singularity Milestone Release
        </p>
 
       <p style="font-size: larger; font-weight: bold">
          20 October 2005 - Singularity 1.0-M1 Release
        </p>
        <p>
         Singularity Milestone Release
        </p>

      </subsection>

      
      <subsection name="Help and Feedback">
        <p>
          If you have any questions, suggestions or comments about Singularity or
          this website, please feel free to post them to the
          <a href="mail-lists.html">Singularity users mailing list</a>.
        </p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="Release Information">
        <p>
          The current stable Singularity release is version 0.0 and can be obtained from the
          <a href="start/download.html">download page</a>.
        </p>
        <p>
          
        </p>
        <p>
          
        </p>
      </subsection>

    </section>
    <section name="Requirements">
      <p>Be careful, the following plugins must be installed to build the Singularity project :</p>
      <ul>
        <li>maven-findbugs-plugin 0.9.2 (at least)</li>
        <li>maven-checkstyle-plugin 2.4.1 (at least)</li>
      </ul>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>